{
    "subject": "resource/List_of_counties_in_Texas",
    "predicate": "property/num",
    "object": "443",
    "human_readable": "The list of counties in Texas has a total number of 443.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8302270770072937,
            "question": "What is the total number of counties in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7157287001609802,
            "question": "How many counties are there in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6848151683807373,
            "question": "Is the number of counties in Texas a significant number?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.537286102771759,
            "question": "Is the number of counties in Texas more than 400?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4674767255783081,
            "question": "What geographic unit comprises a county in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43932369351387024,
            "question": "Could you name some counties in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.400273859500885,
            "question": "Would you say the number of counties in Texas is high or low compared to other states?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38231778144836426,
            "question": "Are there more than 200 counties in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3113629221916199,
            "question": "What is the smallest number of counties that could exist in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2562776505947113,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between population and the number of counties?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The list of counties in Texas has a total number of 443.",
            "html": "dbpedia_176_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the smallest number of counties that could exist in Texas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_176_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there more than 200 counties in Texas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_176_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you say the number of counties in Texas is high or low compared to other states?",
            "html": "dbpedia_176_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_176_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe documents clearly state that Texas has 254 counties, not 443. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that there are 254 counties in Texas, not 443. Therefore, the statement claiming the list of counties in Texas has a total number of 443 is incorrect according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}